SARAH BARBER

PROSPECTIVE INTERN



+1 (336) 875-1798



Smbarber2@uncq.edu



1010 Kildare Rd, Asheboro, NC, 27203



LinkedIn

OBJECTIVE

I am a computer science student interested in getting hands-on experience before graduating. I currently work at the Esports Gaming Arena on campus, so I have a lot of experience with tech support, team management, and customer service, but I'd like to find an internship that can offer me work more focused on computer science itself. I recently spent a semester studying abroad in Nagoya, Japan, so I have experience navigating a new culture and dealing with any problems that may arise due to that.

EXPERIENCE

June 2024 – Present

Esports Arena PA • UNCG: Recreation and Wellness

- Organize and send out staff schedules, arrange meetings, and balance expense and inventory reports.
- Partner with Innovate UNCG to entertain both students and sponsors of the arena itself.
- Manage a staff of 20 college students to ensure that the arena is running smoothly.

April 2022 - Present

Esports Arena Supervisor • UNCG: Recreation and Wellness

- Set up and performed upkeep on a range of different electronics, such as PCs, gaming consoles, and Shoutcasting equipment.
- Assisted in the running of engagement events and programs for students within the arena.

October 2020 - Present

Seasonal Poll Worker • Randolph County Board of Elections

 Monitored members of the public for compliance with security measures and other procedures.

August 2019 - September 2019

Administrative Assistant • Sedgwick

- Established a record filing system to improve document organization and management.
- Filled, labeled, and prepared packages for shipment.

EDUCATION

University of North Carolina at Greensboro, NC

- 3.8 GPA
- COMPUTER SCIENCE MAJOR
- IT MINOR
- MEMBER OF THE LLOYD
 INTERNATIONAL HONORS
 COLLEGE
- STUDIED ABROAD IN JAPAN
 AT NAGOYA UNIVERSITY FOR
 FOREIGN STUDY

KEY SKILLS

- NATIVE SPANISH SPEAKER
 WITH EXPERIENCE
 TRANSLATING
- NOVICE JAPANESE (STUDIED ABROAD)
- CUSTOMER SERVICE
- IAVA PROGRAMMING
- HTML PROGRAMMING
- MYSQL PROGRAMMING
- WEB APP DEVELOPMENT
- PROGRAM MANAGEMENT
- TECH SUPPORT
- SECRETARIAL DUTIES

June 2018 – August 2019

Maker Mentor • Summer Camp Counselor • UNCG

- Implemented STEM based camp activities focusing on physical, social, and emotional growth.
- Organized and guided group activities by mentoring, helping and participating with campers.

LEADERSHIP

While I do work as a PA for the Esports arena and manage the dayby-day proceedings of the arena, I am also currently the president and founder of the UNCG Game Development Coalition on campus. This club is dedicated to the unification of different academic departments on campus to bring students together to create video games. Our goal is to strengthen the bonds between students and let students put their skills to use in the form of video game development.

REFERENCES

Matthew Fisher, Former Colleague

Email: msfishe2@uncg.edu

Zach Ephlin, Current Employer Email: z_ephlin@uncg.edu

AWARDS

- EMPLOYEE OF THE YEAR 2023
- RECIPIENT OF THE CHANCELLOR'S
 SCHOLARSHIP
- RECIPIENT OF THE BLUE AND GOLD SCHOLARSHIP